const quizDB = [
    {
        question: "Q1: What is a correct syntax to output 'Hello World' in C++?",
        a: 'echo "Hello World";',
        b: 'cout<<"Hello World";',
        c: 'echo("Hello World)";',
        d: 'p("Hello World)";',
        ans: "ans2"

    },
    {
        question: "Q2: C++ is an alias of C#",
        a: 'True',
        b: 'False',
        c: 'Can not Say',
        d: 'None',
        ans: "ans2"

    },
    {
        question: "Q3: Which data type is used to create a variable that should store text?",
        a: 'Txt',
        b: 'String',
        c: 'string',
        d: 'myString',
        ans: "ans3"

    },
    {
        question: "Q4: How do you create a variable with the numeric value 5?",
        a: 'int x = 5;',
        b: 'double x = 5;',
        c: 'num x = 5;',
        d: 'x = 5;',
        ans: "ans1"

    },
    {
        question: "Q5: How do you create a variable with the floating number 2.8?",
        a: 'byte x = 2.8;',
        b: 'double x = 2.8;',
        c: 'int x = 2.8;',
        d: 'x = 2.8;',
        ans: "ans2"

    },
    {
        question: "Q6: Which method can be used to find the length of a string?",
        a: 'length()',
        b: 'getLength()',
        c: 'len()',
        d: 'getSize();',
        ans: "ans1"

    },
    {
        question: "Q7: The value of a string variable can be surrounded by single quotes.",
        a: 'True',
        b: 'False',
        c: 'Can not Say',
        d: 'None',
        ans: "ans2"

    },
    {
        question: "Q8: Which header file lets us work with input and output objects?",
        a: '#include<iostram>',
        b: '#include<iostring>',
        c: '#include<inputstr>',
        d: '#include<stram>',
        ans: "ans1"

    },
    {
        question: "Q9: To declare an array in C++, define the variable type with:",
        a: '{}',
        b: '()',
        c: 'None',
        d: '[]',
        ans: "ans4"

    },
    {
        question: "Q10: Array indexes start with:",
        a: '0',
        b: '-1',
        c: '1',
        d: '2',
        ans: "ans1"

    },
    {
        question: "Q11: How do you create a function in C++?",
        a: 'functionName.',
        b: 'functionName[]',
        c: '(functionName)',
        d: 'functionName()',
        ans: "ans4"

    },
    {
        question: "Q12: How do you create a function in C++?",
        a: 'functionName.',
        b: 'functionName[]',
        c: '(functionName)',
        d: 'functionName()',
        ans: "ans4"

    },
    {
        question: "Q13: Which keyword is used to create a class in C++?",
        a: 'className',
        b: 'myClass',
        c: 'class',
        d: 'class()',
        ans: "ans3"

    },
    {
        question: "Q14: What is the correct way to create an object called myObj of MyClass?",
        a: 'MyClass myObj;',
        b: 'new myObj = MyClass();',
        c: 'class MyClass = new myObj();',
        d: 'class myObj = new MyClass();',
        ans: "ans1"

    },
    {
        question: "Q15: In C++, it is possible to inherit attributes and methods from one class to another.",
        a: 'True',
        b: 'False',
        c: 'None',
        d: 'Can not Say',
        ans: "ans1"

    },
    {
        question: "Q16: Which method can be used to find the highest value of x and y?",
        a: 'maxNum(x,y)',
        b: 'largest(x,y)',
        c: 'max(x,y)',
        d: 'maximum(x,y)',
        ans: "ans3"

    },
    {
        question: "Q17: How do you create a reference variable of an existing variable?",
        a: 'With REF Word',
        b: 'With * Operator',
        c: 'With ref Word',
        d: 'With the & operator',
        ans: "ans4"

    },
    {
        question: "Q18: Which keyword is used to return a value inside a method?",
        a: 'break',
        b: 'return',
        c: 'void',
        d: 'get',
        ans: "ans2"

    },
    {
        question: "Q19: Which statement is used to stop a loop?",
        a: 'break',
        b: 'return',
        c: 'void',
        d: 'get',
        ans: "ans1"

    },
]